All right, guys. Um, we got two Georgia
Bulldogs today. So, quite the
coincidence there. Uh, turned out pretty
well for us. Obviously, uh, I'll just
start with some highlights. Uh, you
know, drafting Christian in the second
round. Um, you know, four-year player at
Georgia. Uh, two-year starter. Um, as we
went through this process, we had a
formal interview with him at the
combine. Um, Peter Surman actually
worked him out at Georgia. Uh, funny
story there. was supposed to go, but the
uh TSA issues at the uh airport kind of
created a bit little bit of an issue
there. So, Peter happened to be
somewhere else close by and he hopped in
the car and drove over there and worked
him out. And so, uh it all worked out.
But great player, love his energy, love
his juice. I think you guys already
sense that and kind of his media
obligation so far. His versatility and
his play style is going to be really
good for us. And so, uh great move
there. And then Oscar Del in the third
round. Um you know, we had a formal
interview with Oscar at the combine. He
kind of shared I think a little bit of
that. Josh Hill went and worked him out
and so we got exposure to both these
guys. Felt really comfortable with that
through this whole process. He's a
multi- spot guy. He's played a lot of
different positions in his career there.
He's played with some other tight end so
he knows how to kind of play that you
know multi-tighten uh type role and u
you know that was a great opportunity
for us obviously uh you know for him to
still be available in the third round
was a nice luxury for us and so two
really good players to add to this thing
and we'll just keep going tomorrow. So,
>> coach Bach in line so long he missed his
flight.
>> Uh, we just had issues with kind of
logistics and travel and all that sort
of stuff. That was uh that was that
Sunday Monday. Uh, you know, a lot of
guys had issues with airports with uh
TSA issues and so uh a lot of our
coaches there's a lot of funny stories
associated with a lot of our coaches
ended up shifting gears and covering
other people and you know some people
hopped in cars and just started driving
really far away and uh just to connect
with these guys. So, it was fun. Was it
was these two guys kind of in a bullpen,
if you will, at those rounds or did they
kind of surprise you when they were
there?
>> Well, yeah. I think we felt great about
both of these guys. Obviously, you're
going to get to pick one of them in the
second round. Uh felt great about
Christian. We're hoping, you know, he
was certainly in that clump of guys
we're hoping was going to be available
for us in this situation. And then, uh,
you know, as the third round progressed,
uh, having Oscar still available, I
think that was a certainly a great
opportunity for us just to add to that
group. Again, we feel great about our
tight ends and now we get to add him
into that position and people know the
way, you know, this league's trending
with the ability to play in multiple
tight end sets and that's that's a
valuable asset. And so, uh, you know,
there's nothing wrong with having a few
of those guys that you can play with.
>> When you have a guy like Delt utilized
in sort of a hyperspecific way at
Georgia, what are some of the traits
that you were looking for to identify
how he might fit differently if used
differently in your system?
>> Yeah, I think he's got a number of
things that will come to the table.
Obviously, we recognize the athleticism
that he provides. You know, he he does a
great job out in space. He's got some
juice, some some speed, vertical speed.
I think he's a very willing, physical
run player. I think that's an important
aspect. Certainly, we know um you know,
with Jawan and Noah and the other guys
we have, like we got some guys who can
make some some play with the the ball in
their hands. And so, you know, these
guys are going to have to do some dirty
work and he's ready for that. And I
think one of the things that he maybe
hasn't done as much, but he'll certainly
be ready to do and I think he'll embrace
just the special teams component of
that. You know, I think uh he's got
every trait you can possibly think of to
be a really good special teams player.
And so I'm excited to see him develop
there.
>> Is he someone like like when you watch
him and then you look at the numbers,
like to me it just kind of like he looks
different than he does on paper. Like is
that a fair assessment maybe of like his
receiving ability that there's more
there than maybe 200 yards a season or
whatever? Yeah, I I think it's it's a
byproduct sometimes of, you know,
Georgia has a phenomenal formula of
playing really successful football and,
you know, you can look at it uh with a
lot of their offensive players. You
know, the receiver room and the tighter
room. There's just not going to be as
many uh pass catching opportunities in
their seasons. And so they do an
excellent job of, you know, controlling
games. They have, you know, one of the
best defenses every single year in in
college football. And so, uh, he played
with some other guys early in his
career. And so, um, you know, he's kind
of had this, you know, 20 in the 20s.
let's call it. Um, you know, catches per
per season, but uh, you know, he does a
lot of other other pieces I think that
all add to the sum of a really good
player. And so, um, yeah, he's got
plenty of really good football, some of
his best football moving forward.
>> Do you think he has like real like
two-way ability to to kind of really
excel both
>> in the running pass?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah, absolutely. I think uh, you
know, he's got some really good
versatility. I think, you know, the way
they, you know, played him, obviously he
played a little bit more of like an off
the- ball tight end, uh, in a wing
alignment a lot of times, uh, you know,
he'll be able to play potentially in the
back field on on the line of scrimmage
and off the ball. And so, uh, yeah, I
think what we're getting is a really
smart player. I think he's really he
he'll be able to handle some volume and
I think it'll he'll allow us to play the
chess piece game when you have Jawan and
you have Noah and you have these other
tight ends that you want to kind of put
in certain positions, he'll be able to
kind of counteract with those guys.
>> Is Josh Hill the right comp for him?
That's a great We should We should throw
Josh up in the interview process and
let's let's ask him. But, uh, Josh felt
great about him. You know, Chase, Josh,
those guys were fired up. Uh, I think
our coaching staff really had a really
good vision for, you know, how this guy
can play with those other tight ends.
And again, um, the value of playing in
multiple tight end positions um, is
valuable. You know, you can see the
teams that made runs this year. A lot of
them are playing in 12 and 13 personnel.
Um, and we think there's still the pass
game juice that these guys provide
because of what, you know, those guys
have in the pass game I think is going
to be a benefit. These guys aren't a
bunch of, you know, just big wise.
They're just going to block and, you
know, when we get in 13 personnel, it's
kind of a ding-ding. I think, you know,
we can do a lot of things with those
guys.
>> Do Christian
complent each other or will they compete
like for one of the same spots like
>> No, they they can play they can
certainly play on the field at the same
time. I think uh you know one of the
thing that Christian has done is he's
played a number of spots across the
front and I think that versatility is
going to provide you with some fun chest
piece games. Um you know he's certainly
played you know plenty of nose but he
he'll play the shade. He'll work his way
out all the way out to five technique
and some three four structures and so um
you know he's going to provide some
really good versatility and and that
group uh it's great to add one to that
piece. Uh you know defensive linemen are
hard to find in this league and uh he's
a talented one. that versatility that
did that character just his attitude
kind of also like a great selling point
of why he went in the draft.
>> Yeah, we we had a fun interview process
with him and uh you get a little dose of
who he is and so uh we're fired up to
have him here. I know like all these
guys there's a ton of hard work moving
forward to you know you got to get
acclimated from college to to the NFL. I
think coming from a Georgia is a really
um beneficial thing for both of these
guys. They're as prepared as anyone you
can imagine. But, uh, you know, there'll
be a transition, but I think he's ready
to work his tail off and get ready to
go.
>> Both of these, uh, players very
physical. They talked about in the media
availability
>> and even your the wide receiver, the
Tyson, he loves to block. Yeah.
>> Is that the number one trait you wanted
this draft?
>> I think it's an important trait. Um,
>> you know, you got to run the football on
offense. We got to stop the run on
defense. U, that leads to so many
things. Uh, but this game's a physical
game and so no matter what position
you're playing, uh, we went through with
Jordan yesterday, like, you know,
receivers got to be physical. They got
to be physical in the run game. They got
to be physical in the pass game, these
corners u are going to press you in this
league. They're not going to play off
like like college football maybe tends
to. Um, you know, then when you get, you
know, interior D line tight ends are
going to play some dirty work. I mean,
there's there's nothing uh easy about
those job responsibilities in this
league. And so, uh, I think we got
really high character guys that are
going to do it.
>> When I would say that kind of generally
You're looking you're looking for guys
who can help you in multiple different
ways.
>> Jordan being able to play all three
positions and Oscar being passer.
>> Yeah, I think I think that's key. I
think uh you know our rosters have a
certain size to them and I think it's
important that you have guys who can uh
provide multiple opportunities to help
help the football team. And so uh you
know we feel like all three of these
guys will have the versatility that they
need and you know they'll they'll
provide a really good role for them. you
get two guys that are teammates in
college like this and and like a couple
times last year as well. Do you
>> just during the pre-draft process, do
you talk to them about one another? Do
you ever check in like do you utilize
that at all? Sometimes during the draft
process, we like to ask and prompt the
questions of uh Jeff always does a great
job with this is you know if you're
coming to our organization like who's
the culture player that you want to
bring you know and then sometimes who's
the best player that you want to bring
and sometimes it prompts us you know
ideas and sometimes maybe we ask who's
the best player you played against and
so I think anytime you get to collect
those different questions get the
answers to them uh you collect as much
information as you can but uh you know
certainly having guys who have a
relationship that kind know each other.
You know, certainly, you know, Tyler and
Quincy last year and we we've seen that
throughout this thing. Um, you know,
there there's benefits to that.
>> Did Oscar or Christian mentioned one
another when
>> I don't recall. I'll have to look back
through our notes.
>> Kelly, before you got here, this team
didn't used to make all the draft picks
up
is elite. Um,
>> yeah. it has there been a conscious
effort for because of the state of this
roster to try and and lead with as many
picks as you enter these drafts with or
have there been a lot of
>> I think there's plenty of conversations
about moving up constantly. I think it's
just a matter of, you know, finding the
right value and right situation and, you
know, hey, we we've done that, you know,
certainly we've had conversations even
today about that. Um, but we understand
we got great opportunities to add to
this team and um, you know, certainly
when you look at from this perspective,
as many opportunities and swings as you
can get, you know, that's a positive
thing and for for us, we feel like, you
know, we're still getting really
talented players are certainly going to
help our team. was value kind of maybe
one of the reasons why you guys didn't
take an edge rush today or anything like
that.
>> Well, I think there's there's plenty of
conversations and still certainly we
have another whole day of this. Um, you
know, you you get you build a board and
you trust your board and you have plenty
of conversations as you go and certainly
there's conversations and you got to
make make decisions. You know, there's
guys that we love. There's you know, I
think that's the hardest part of this
draft is we invest so much time into
this process. we kind of fall in love
with a lot of these players and then you
only get to Yeah, you got to pick one in
in each, you know, situation and you got
to go and, you know, you're going to
miss out on a few other opportunities.
>> How much are you guys also weighing that
like, you know, all the players that are
still available, but also some of the
veterans that could be available in the
trade market or in the second wave of
free agency after like after the draft?
How are you going to weigh all those?
>> Yeah, I mean, player acquisitions, year-
round process. Um, you know, we're going
to have obviously an opportunity to sign
guys here. Hopefully sign some guys who
maybe don't get drafted and then there's
plenty of veterans out there that you're
going to have continued conversations
with. And so, uh, that goes all the way,
you know, all the way through training
camp in into the season. We know how
these things go. And, um, while this is
a very, very important part of building
our roster and building our team, it's,
you know, certainly very well
recognized, there's a lot of other
opportunities to keep going. Was back
Georgia uh influencing your time in
Philly at all?
>> No. No. But yeah, certainly How's done
it a few times. So,
>> what do you see as the potential
benefits of having um
you know, two
skilled players in the passing game
coming in on the heels of a young
quarterback establishing himself as a
starter and them kind of going through
this together?
Yeah, I think certainly we're trying to
build a group that hopefully, you know,
has some continuity and and works
together for a number of years. And so,
um, you know, certainly when you look at
what Jordan's hopefully going to provide
for us, the the connection with him and
Tyler and, you know, I think, you know,
Oscar has just turned into a great
situation. We feel great about our tight
end room. You know, to add Noah during
the offseason process to now get Oscar
on board and to have a number of other
guys that we were able to, you know,
keep on our roster, we're in a really
healthy spot. And you know, I think the
more those guys spend time together and
and work through this entire OTAA
process into the summer program, into
training camp, uh there's a lot of time
that needs to be invested into this.
But, uh, you know, we got the right kind
of guys to kind of, you know, work
together on that.
>> I know you mentioned Kristen's vers
versatility
does like I guess when you're first
installing, I mean, does he project as
as a guy playing the same position as
God actually, or is that just something
he'll do on occasion? Yeah, I think I
think it's about giving guys kind of a
home base to start and then we just got
to get out on the field with these guys.
We got we got to let them go and you
know, we'll we'll make those adjustments
as we go, but uh what we feel like is
we're bringing a really really talented
player, really good person for our
locker room into a group that um will
provide some depth. You know, certainly,
you know, it's it's hard to acquire big
guys and so uh we'll add them to that
mix and we'll kind of see how it goes.
Can you make some acquisitions that you
guys might like in free agency and the
first few picks on offense allows you
guys to be like maybe a little bit more
versatile than you guys were last year
in terms of personal package wanted to
play more 12 or 11 or just be a little
bit more how you see that?
>> Yeah, I think that's a fair assessment.
I think we do feel like we have a lot of
guys who hey, they got a lot of
versatility. They're really smart
football players. Um, you know, more
time together uh through this whole
process and so uh all that stuff will
build.
seem pretty excited about the idea of
lining up next to Brian Brazie was kind
of
assessment of, you know, how those two
can complement one another.
>> Yeah, I think we're adding them to a
group that, um, has, you know, a nice
mix. There's some veterans in there. Uh,
Shep, God, uh, but then some young guys,
you know, and some young guys. And so,
um, you know, we're going to need a
number of those guys. We're going to
need a number of them to play. uh you
play in three four structures. We're
going to play with three in base, but uh
you know there's plenty of sub packages
that you got to be able to utilize to
stop the run to play in passing
situations and so u the depth is going
to be important there character and team
captains and guys with high character.
Uh you put a lot of importance a lot of
importance on that as far as rating
players.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No question. And I think uh
you know we spend just as much time. We
can watch we can all watch the film and
figure out the the player usually and
you know kind of put them in a category
of some kind. But we got to get to know
the people. This is a uh tough hard
business. This is the NFL. Uh there's
nothing easy about it. The players
individually are going to go through
highs and lows. We're going to go
through highs and lows collect
collectively as a team. And so we need
the right kind of guys to do that.
>> Was the um with Peter driving to
Georgia. Was that for Georgia's program
or an individual workout just with
>> It was a private workout. Yeah.
>> Hey, K, what are those moments like you
when you making that phone call? Those
players like how Christians react to the
ride like
>> Yeah.
>> What's that like for you?
>> They're special. Uh, you know, for these
guys, I mean, all these guys have had
such a, you know, amazing one-of-a-kind
ride to get to the position that they're
in. Uh there's highs, there's lows, and
they get, you know, most often they get
to be surrounded by the people who help
them get there the most. And so, uh,
those are really special moments. It's
really, really cool. It's uh one of the
one of the best moments I think in the
NFL is when you get to hear those
conversations and hear them celebrate
and because hey these guys have earned
it now. There's a ton of work ahead.
It's going to be even harder than what
they've gone through. But uh you know
it's a cool moment for those guys.
>> Could you share with us you know talk a
little bit about the shirts you're
wearing? Autism awareness you know uh
we're special for the organization for
special need kids
>> in. Yeah. I think it's just awesome
awareness. I think, you know, for our
organization, I've been here for 2
years, but I know they've done it longer
than this. Uh, just taking advantage of
the opportunity and the platform that,
you know, the NFL draft provides and so,
uh, drawing awareness to it. I know, uh,
you know, Kai and Jeff and Mickey and
those guys have put so much effort into
this and, uh, drawing attention to it
and I think it's really cool to, you
know, our entire war room was, uh, you
know, all wearing these and, uh, it was
a lot of fun.
>> Everything is, uh, good on on Del's
health. I know he did skip all the
combine drills, but like he ended up
working out pro days. So,
>> yeah, we went we went through the
medical process. Obviously, we feel
comfortable.
>> Is um
Vernon
Christians
off
Vernon's working. Vernon's working.
Yeah, he's been doing great.